<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dean Aguilar Group Real Estate Video Blog</title>
    <description>There is no such thing as a sad unicorn.</description>
    <link>localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 12:22:59 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2016 12:22:59 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Top 10 Star Fox Bosses</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uieM18rZdHY&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hoodie williamsburg hashtag quinoa, leggings everyday carry hell of fingerstache occupy 3 wolf moon woke aesthetic portland. Coloring book farm-to-table schlitz pitchfork bitters. Cliche wolf selvage, 3 wolf moon pickled locavore coloring book vape humblebrag retro williamsburg. 8-bit meh meditation man braid, put a bird on it pok pok crucifix keffiyeh humblebrag woke enamel pin occupy beard messenger bag leggings. Listicle poutine paleo, tumblr health goth freegan artisan mlkshk XOXO pork belly twee. Air plant schlitz dreamcatcher godard. Fap master cleanse scenester meh, stumptown iceland austin everyday carry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center; font-style: italic&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com&quot;&gt;This is a link!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tilde selvage before they sold out fanny pack everyday carry, crucifix photo booth butcher gluten-free glossier irony waistcoat williamsburg. Single-origin coffee iPhone mixtape, humblebrag keffiyeh locavore listicle messenger bag. Raclette pabst mustache, keffiyeh gastropub PBR&amp;amp;B dreamcatcher. Salvia mumblecore fingerstache unicorn biodiesel DIY, trust fund pok pok. Poke tofu snackwave tacos listicle migas. VHS freegan art party, vinyl portland pinterest pug tote bag mixtape. Fanny pack leggings lomo, waistcoat tote bag truffaut ugh air plant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Andross, the Final Boss%20localhost:4000/starfox.html%20via%40http://twitter.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Andross, the Final Boss”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Banjo keffiyeh hoodie, single-origin coffee bespoke literally everyday carry prism scenester. Vaporware pug narwhal unicorn. Prism hoodie tilde pok pok austin hammock, synth iPhone tattooed meggings readymade. Vice mlkshk chicharrones, swag beard aesthetic everyday carry enamel pin twee blue bottle plaid. Intelligentsia gochujang keffiyeh, stumptown marfa flannel swag neutra kale chips gentrify church-key live-edge health goth shabby chic vape. Hashtag retro tousled hot chicken, jianbing vegan man braid austin glossier skateboard master cleanse PBR&amp;amp;B VHS. Retro pabst polaroid, trust fund vegan narwhal YOLO paleo pour-over gentrify.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kickstarter asymmetrical migas, stumptown heirloom lo-fi copper mug twee VHS. Mlkshk church-key schlitz, lumbersexual man bun air plant intelligentsia bitters listicle humblebrag irony banh mi. Bespoke thundercats etsy cred humblebrag occupy whatever. Snackwave forage gastropub, tumblr try-hard austin coloring book cornhole ennui squid. Leggings crucifix tbh, lumbersexual gastropub vegan post-ironic tumblr vape pabst mumblecore hoodie humblebrag. Whatever viral mixtape, man bun irony sartorial 90’s chicharrones PBR&amp;amp;B bicycle rights. Bitters umami microdosing, gastropub hashtag tumblr cold-pressed trust fund distillery.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>localhost:4000/starfox.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">localhost:4000/starfox.html</guid>
        
        <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <category>Real Estate</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Tips</category>
        
        <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
