<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Dean Aguilar Group Real Estate Podcast</title>
    <link>http://deanaguilarrealestate.com</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://deanaguilarrealestate.com"/>
    <description>The Dean Aguilar Group is a team comprised of high-performing San Diegans. As a top 1% real estate team, we have over 45 years of experience in the San Diego market. We want to provide up-to-the-minute market information so that our clients can make the best real estate decisions possible. Tune into this podcast to learn all of the latest tips, trends, and market updates.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Dean Aguilar</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2016-11-17 10:13:07 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Dean Aguilar</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://deanaguilarrealestate.com/img/aguilar_podcast.png"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">News &amp; Politics</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>dean@deanaguilargroup.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Dean Aguilar</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Dean Aguilar</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://deanaguilarrealestate.com/img/aguilar_podcast.png"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the San Diego Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>The Dean Aguilar Group is a team comprised of high-performing San Diegans. As a top 1% real estate team, we have over 45 years of experience in the San Diego market. We want to provide up-to-the-minute market information so that our clients can make the best real estate decisions possible. Tune into this podcast to learn all of the latest tips, trends, and market updates.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>4 Tips to Sell Your Home Quickly and for More Money</title>
        <link>http://deanaguilarrealestate.com/4-tips-to-sell-your-home-quickly-and-for-more-money.html</link>
        
          <category>Real Estate</category>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Dean Aguilar</author>
        <pubDate>2016-11-09 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Dean+Aguilar/Videos/4+Tips+For+Sellers.mp4</guid>
        <description>

If you are thinking about selling your home for the first time, here are four tips to help you sell quickly and for top dollar.

If you’re a first-time home seller, there are a few things you should know before listing your home on the market. Here are my four tips to sell your home quickly and for more money:


  Price your home accurately from the beginning. There are a few reasons behind this. One reason is that home buyers have their searches set up for a certain price point, so overpricing it may shrink your buyer pool. Secondly, once your home hits the MLS, if it’s priced properly, you have a much better opportunity to receive multiple offers right away. Also, when a home is overpriced, a buyer may either write a lowball offer or assume that there is something wrong with it and avoid writing an offer entirely.
  Clear the clutter from the home. Prospective buyers want to be able to visualize themselves in your home. Removing the knickknacks and larger furniture will give these buyers a better idea of what the home is going to look like when they purchase it.
  Put the upgrade money where it counts. If you’re thinking about investing in your home, my recommendation would be to make small upgrades. A new coat of neutral paint or new carpeting are very small improvements you can make that will make a world of difference in the eyes of the buyer.
  Marketing, marketing, marketing. Make sure that the real estate professional you hire has a full and solid marketing plan from beginning to end and that they have a strong online presence so that your home stays top of mind in this fast-moving market.


“Buyers want to be able to visualize themselves in your home.”

Keep these four tips in mind, and you’ll be well on your way to a successful home sale. If you have any other questions about the home selling process or you’re thinking about buying real estate in our area, give me a call or send me an email. I’d be happy to help you!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Dean+Aguilar/Videos/4+Tips+For+Sellers.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://deanaguilarrealestate.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Dean+Aguilar/Videos/4+Tips+For+Sellers.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the San Diego Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Dean Aguilar</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>If you are thinking about selling your home for the first time, here are four tips to help you sell quickly and for top dollar.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Should You List Your Home During the Fall?</title>
        <link>http://deanaguilarrealestate.com/should-you-list-your-home-during-the-fall.html</link>
        
          <category>Home Seller Tips</category>
        
        <author>Dean Aguilar</author>
        <pubDate>2016-10-25 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>

If you’re thinking about listing your home and are worried that the summer selling season is over, I have some good news for you—the fall is actually a great time to list your home. Why is this? Here are my top four reasons:

1. Demand is strong. With pending transactions up nearly 18% since last year, there are still a lot of buyers out there looking to buy homes. The low inventory levels in our area are creating more multiple offer situations, which is great news for you as a seller.

2. There is less competition on the market. With school back in session and the holidays just around the corner, there are fewer listings on the market, which provides you a great opportunity to pick off the buyer pool.

“Low inventory and high demand make fall a great time to sell.”

3. The lending process is quicker. Because lenders are generally inundated with applications during the spring and summer, the loan process will generally take anywhere from 30 to 35 days. In the fall, however, we’ve seen loans close as quickly as 17 to 21 days.

4. Now is a great time to move up. With home prices expected to increase 5.3% next year and builder confidence increasing, you’re presented with a great opportunity to move into the home of your dreams, saving you money on your down payment and mortgage payment.

If you have any other questions about buying or selling a home during the fall, give me a call or send me an email. I look forward to talking with you soon!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://deanaguilarrealestate.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the San Diego Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Dean Aguilar</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>If you’re wondering whether the fall is a good time to sell your home, I have some good news for you. Here are four reasons why fall is still a great time to sell.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Diego, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Dean Aguilar</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Dean Aguilar</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">The Dean Aguilar Group is a team comprised of high-performing San Diegans. As a top 1% real estate team, we have over 45 years of experience in the San Diego market. We want to provide up-to-the-minute market information so that our clients can make the best real estate decisions possible. Tune into this podcast to learn all of the latest tips, trends, and market updates.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
